{
    "subject": "resource/Voice_of_OC",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Santa_Ana,_California",
    "human_readable": "The location of Voice of OC is Santa Ana, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8218362927436829,
            "question": "Where is Voice of OC located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7976827621459961,
            "question": "In which city is Voice of OC situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7366413474082947,
            "question": "What state is the location of Voice of OC in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47349175810813904,
            "question": "Is Voice of OC located on the West Coast?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42467015981674194,
            "question": "What are some other notable organizations located in Santa Ana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2770604193210602,
            "question": "Can you name a media outlet headquartered in Santa Ana, California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24893808364868164,
            "question": "Is Santa Ana a coastal city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23949693143367767,
            "question": "What type of organization is Voice of OC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21129187941551208,
            "question": "What is the population of Santa Ana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12825660407543182,
            "question": "Does Santa Ana have a large media presence?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location of Voice of OC is Santa Ana, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7668_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Santa Ana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7668_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of organization is Voice of OC?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7668_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Santa Ana a coastal city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7668_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7668_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7668_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7668_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7668_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7668_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7668_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7668_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7668_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7668_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7668_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the location of Voice of OC is indeed Santa Ana, California. The document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7668/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt` mentions that \"Voice Of OC is a non-profit news organization based in Santa Ana, CA\". This confirms the location of Voice of OC."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions that Voice Of OC is based in Santa Ana, CA. This directly supports the statement that the location of Voice of OC is Santa Ana, California."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}